In the not-too-distant future
Next Sunday A.D.
There was a guy named Joel
Not too different from you or me
He worked at Gizmonic Institute
Just another face
in a red jumpsuit
He did a good job
cleaning up the place
But his bosses
didn't like him
So they shot him
into space
We'll send him
cheesy movies
The worst we can find
La-la-la
He'll have to sit
and watch them all
And we'll monitor his mind
La-la-la
Now, keep in mind
Joel can't control
Where the movies
begin or end
La-la-la
Because he used
those special parts
To make his robot friends
-Robot Roll Call:
-All right, let's go!
-Cambot!
-Pan left!
-Gypsy!
-Hi, girl!
-Tom Servo!
-What a cool guy!
-Crow!
-Oh, wisecracker.
If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
And other science facts
La-la-la
Then repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show"
"I should really just relax"
For Mystery Science Theater
3000!
IBM, CBS, RCA, the CIA,
the FBI, the NBA,
A&P, NBC, ABC,
R. Crumb, and C.P.O. Sharkey.
You see, they're all the same.
And what do I think?
I think, if life
gives you lemons,
you make lemonade.
Good night, and may God bless.
Hey, that was great.
Hey, I didn't know
you guys were there.
-Stop, thank... thank you.
-I'd applaud if I could, but...
Well, it's a work in progress.
It's part of my one-man show
called "Robot on the Run."
Wow, it's... Hey, look,
we're on, everybody. Hi!
Hey, welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
We're having our
art Chautauqua today.
Cool.
FEMALE VOICE: Commercial sign
in 15 seconds.
Anyway, Tom,
you wanna do yours?
Let's do it.
[ Tom clears throat ]
I was born the son
of a poor Filipino merchant.
I remember I would sit on the
stoop of my tenement brownstone
on the Lower East Side.
I was... Uh, I was, uh...
FEMALE VOICE: Tom, your line is,
"I was crying."
Thank you.
FEMALE VOICE:
Commercial sign in five,
four, three, two...
Commercial sign now.
I was crying.
[ Whimpers ]
[ Sobbing ]
Now?
Mayo, I'm going to make
a recommendation
that you be dropped
from the program.
Don't you do it!
I've got nowhere else to go!
I've got nothin'.
-Hey, pretty good.
-Yeah, pretty good.
-Thank you. Huh, Cool.
-Okay, anyway, I...
...think it's time to do, uh,
the invention exchange here.
What I've got isn't really
a new invention,
but it's a new kind
of guitar chord.
What you do...
It's for the dynamic endings
of your rock show.
This is the Mel Bay, uh,
chart right there.
It's an A minor augmented
with an Eddie Van Halen
bolt action on the bottom.
Cool.
And so when you get
to the big jams
at the end of the concert,
you can play it. Now...
It takes two hands
to play this chord,
so at that point you have
your dynamic front man.
I guess Crow will do it...
will strum it.
Okay, on the count of three.
One, two, three.
[ Long guitar note ]
[ Coughing ]
What do you think, sirs?
Oh, great, get Foghat
on the phone.
Well, our experiment
this week, Joel,
is going to be sweeping
the country by storm.
Isn't that right, Frank?
That's right.
You know, all the fads
with the young people today.
You know the kids today,
with their loud music,
hula hoops, fax machines,
but the biggest fad these days,
karaoke, whoo!
[ Sings poorly ]
What we've done is we've
invented a Karaoke machine
that exclusively plays
public domain songs.
That's right. That means you can
sing into your karaoke machine,
have as much fun as you want,
and not pay one cent
in artist royalties.
That's right, Frank.
Now, what happens when you go
into your favorite karaoke bar
and you want to hear "I Want to
Know What Love is" by Foreigner?
People vomit?
No, Lou Gramm, songwriter
and Chess King spokesmodel
gets a big fat royalty check,
and that means lots of money.
So, Joel, we've loaded
our machine
only with public domain songs.
All free of copyright,
all owned by you, the people.
That's right. You wanna hit
the roll there, Jerry?
You get "The Battle Hymn
of the Republic."
The immortal
"Ba Ba Black Sheep."
The turgid and bittersweet
"Gregorian Chant number 5."
The impish "Twinkle Twinkle
Little Star."
Mozart's the Magic Flute,
and there's so much more.
But your experiment this week,
Joel, is called "Pod People".
It has nothing
to do with pods.
It has nothing to do
with people.
It has everything to do
with hurting.
And we're going to sing you
into it...
with our new public domain
karaoke machine.
Hit it, Frank.
Ave
Maria
-[ Yelling ]
-[ Alarm buzzing ]
JOEL: Boy, it's a good thing we
got those... those new heads on.
TOM: Great experiment, Joel.
Great, great invention there.
JOEL: Oh, pod people got
no reason to live.
TOM: Isn't that Nia Peeples'
brother? Pod Peeple?
-JOEL: Mm-hm.
-TOM: No.
TOM: And she's married
to Maury Povich, right?
JOEL: No, you're thinking of
Connie Chung. That's Cheston.
TOM: Sorry.
CROW: Ooh.
JOEL: William Anton.
I think that's
Susan Anton's half-brother.
-TOM: Could be.
-CROW: Which half?
-TOM: Huh?
-JOEL: Better half?
JOEL: Whoa,
it's the Iron Maiden, dude.
-JOEL: Check him out.
-CROW: Hey! Whoo!
TOM: These...
CROW: I believe I'll use
my putter for...
JOEL: For what?
CROW: For... hittin', guys.
JOEL: Oh, this is
where the Swamp Thing
versus the sweet thang.
-TOM: Ooh.
-CROW: Ah.
TOM: Ah, the tears of a clown.
JOEL: Faruk Alatan? I went
to school with Faruk Alatan.
[ Tom Chuckling ]
TOM: Let's go skin it
and eat it now.
That's not a Spalding.
It's a Piquer Simon-Jack Gray
signature ball.
CROW: Huh.
I dare you to eat it.
TOM: No, you eat it.
Lick it first.
JOEL: That one's hard on pants.
[ Tom groans ]
JOEL: Boy, that guy's got some
unfortunate skin, all right.
TOM: Mm-hm.
-JOEL: Really unfortunate skin.
-TOM: Yeah.
CROW: Emergency 911.
TOM: A man falls.
Stunned by a monster.
JOEL: My baby.
TOM: Oh, boldly backing away
from where no man
has gone before.
CROW: Car sick.
[ Humming
the "Star Trek" theme ]
TOM: Look. Between a rock
and a hard planet.
[ Crow laughs ]
TOM: Come on and dance.
JOEL: I'm Curly Neal,
to show you how.
CROW: It was a dark
and stormy night.
I'd taken
a creative writing course.
JOEL: Daktari.
CROW: Oh, I love taking rides
in the bog.
MAN: You sure this is the place?
MAN 2: Sure I'm sure.
TOM: I'm sure that you're sure
that I'm sure I'm sure.
-CROW: Sure?
-TOM: Sure.
MAN 2: Well, I think I'm sure.
TOM: Think you're sure I'm sure.
CROW: Hey, does he look
dorky enough?
[ Tom laughing ]
TOM: Dorky Park.
And you think you know it all,
don't ya?
TOM: D'oh.
I just don't want to spend
a night out in this crap
for nothin'.
For Christ's sake, will you keep
your voices down?
There's rangers around here.
JOEL: Let's grab the pic-a-nic
baskets and scram, Boo-Boo.
TOM: Meanwhile,
a few miles away.
JOEL: Is this...?
JOEL: Darren,
did you just hear a comet?
[ Thunder rumbling ]
CROW: Huh. Now, this guy's
got Renaissance Festival
written all over him.
JOEL AND TOM: Huzzah!
[ Thunder rumbling ]
ALL: Lions and tigers,
and bears, oh, my!
and bears.
JOEL: Oh, my!
TOM: Well,
time to start camping.
TOM: You dress up
as Oscar Wilde,
and I'll sing Noel Coward songs.
Camping!
[ Chuckling ]
MAN 2: This way.
CROW: Yeah, whatever.
TOM: Tonight on Music
from Hearts of Space,
we'll go on a cosmic joyride
with some space music
by various Bay Area artists.
But first...
[ Thunder rumbling ]
MAN 2: There, that's the nest.
We'll make a fortune
with that lot.
They're nightingale's eggs.
I'll believe that
when they've hatched out.
Lay off. Will you, Matt?
JOEL: Just lay off.
MATT: Here.
JOEL: Perfect.
Go to the truck
and bring a ladder, Sam.
TOM: I didn't get cast in the
Lorne Greene role for nothin'.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
There's something very strange
going on in that light.
Look over there.
Didn't you hear me?
Go get that damn ladder.
-Okay.
-Move it!
Heil Hitler.
JOEL: I'm going, I'm going.
Jeepers.
TOM: First up
on Hearts of Space,
John Tesh with
"Whispering Firestorm."
Then it's Yanni with
"Snoremaster of Trafalgamar."
Then comes Bay Area
musician Del Mondo,
with his Sominex suite
in D-flat.
Then a synthesized
interplanetary salute
to Perry Como.
A the end of the hour,
we'll have information about
the types of sedatives used
by tonight's artists... on Music
from the Hearts of Space.
[ Cat meowing ]
JOEL: Uh, football practice.
[ Meowing continues ]
-TOM: Puma?
-JOEL: Puma.
CROW: Spielberg?
[ Cat whines ]
CROW: Kitty.
Oh, Mittens,
are you eating gerbils?
BOY: Naughty kitty.
JOEL: Must be punished.
Wow, his room's
becoming a disco.
TOM: Neat.
[ Cat meows ]
JOEL: It's
the ABC Movie of the Week.
[ Tom laughs ]
TOM:
Hmm, what pretentious crap.
JOEL: Well, that guy's
going to get
his presidential
physical fitness award.
It's a done deal.
[ Crow grunts ]
[ Tom grunts ]
CROW: Come on, you wuss.
JOEL: Come on,
you gotta want it.
CROW: Hey, Dad
hid the eggs good this year.
[ Man sighs ]
-TOM: Whoa.
-JOEL: That darn cat.
JOEL: Huh?
-TOM: Ooh!
-CROW: Next time on MacGyver.
JOEL: I do believe in spooks.
I do believe in spooks.
I do, I do, I do, I do,
I do, I do. Good night.
TOM: Huzzah!
MAN: Ha! Did you see that?
-TOM: Speak Middle English.
-Did you see it?
What? What the hell are you
talking about?
Looked like... like a huge ball
of fire crashed over there.
-Probably a bolt of lightning.
-It was no bolt of lightning.
I tell you something crashed
back there.
What's going on?
-Well, I just saw something.
-Nothing.
CROW: Here. Hold my purse.
I swear to you, I saw something
crash back there.
I don't know,
maybe a meteorite.
Oh, forget it, Sam.
Just go and get...
TOM: Ready?
Push him over now.
-...the ladder, will you? Go on.
-TOM: Oh... I love that one.
And don't take all night.
Wish we brought Bill along
instead of that crazy moron.
Bill? He's changed sides.
Works for the rangers now.
-JOEL: Bill jumped the fence?
-Bill on the side of the law?
-That's incredible.
-TOM: Swings both ways now.
Let's try that nest over there.
TOM: Hmm.
JOEL: Hey,
looks like Yoda's home.
[ Tom imitating Yoda ]
Luke? Use the Force, Luke.
CROW: Hmm. Nah. Nah.
[ Snorting ]
CROW: Ah, ah, it's clearing now.
JOEL: With a name like Smuckers
raspberry preserves,
you know it's good.
This inflamed tissue,
the burning,
we'd better put some peroxide.
Smuckers brand peroxide.
CROW: I'll get a hanky.
[ Tom clears throat ]
[ Tom retches ]
[ Tom coughing ]
TOM: Welcome to Laserium.
Tonight, music by Rick Wakeman.
[ Tom humming ]
CROW: A ladder.
That's a rope.
Idiot.
[ Tom humming ]
TOM: Oh, forget this.
I'm gettin' out of here.
JOEL: I'm no longer
your whipping boy.
I ain't gonna work
on Maggie's farm no more.
[ Truck grinding gears ]
[ Joel laughing ]
JOEL: If you can't find 'em,
grind 'em, right?
[ Joel continues laughing ]
JOEL: Grind a pound for me, man.
TOM: This Outward Bound
is really broadening him.
[ Man gasps ]
MAN: Well worth the trouble.
Hey, let me have a look.
JOEL: Good idea.
Hmm.
-TOM: What have we here?
-JOEL: These are kola nuts.
JOEL: These are un-kola nuts.
These will pay the rent
for a while.
-Where's Sam?
-CROW: He's paying the rent.
Hell, I don't know.
Should've been back by now,
though.
Hey, what if the son of a...
has run out on us?
And taken the truck, too.
CROW: Don't touch him there.
MAN: Come on.
CROW: Now Mr. Science is going
to show us the white cells.
TOM: Put that down.
TOM: D'oh.
CROW: Oh, clean up
on aisle 7.
JOEL: It's a Gold'n Plump
chicken!
[ Crow retching ]
JOEL: Ugh.
TOM: Ooh, he should've checked
the freshness date on those.
CROW: Over easy.
[ Tom chuckling ]
CROW: Oh, what is he,
an L.A. cop?
TOM: Man exploring
his territory here.
CROW: Ouch.
JOEL: I guess we know which
came first now, don't we?
[ Groaning ]
[ Creature growls ]
CROW: Wanna make a movie,
you gotta break some eggs.
TOM: Bawk, bawk, bawk.
Cluck, cluck, cluck.
JOEL: Oh, my goodness,
it's the Easter Bunny,
and is he ever mad.
CROW: Hey, this guy looks
like Norm Abram getting killed.
-TOM: Hmm.
-CROW: Hear that?
CROW: Sounds like Norm Abram's
getting killed
by a giant chicken.
[ Tom laughing ]
TOM: I gotta walk off
those eggs.
Hoo!
My cholesterol count's way up.
CROW: Morning comes
to cheap white trash.
-Was this it?
-Yeah.
CROW: Yeah.
MATT: I knew it. Son of a...
ran out on us.
MAN: Ah, looks like we spend
the night out here.
JOEL: You feel comfortable, uh,
sharing a sleeping bag with me?
TOM: Ooh.
MATT: All the camping equipment
was in the pickup.
MAN: So what? Won't be the first
time you've dropped it.
Come on.
TOM: D'oh.
TOM: Hey, it's White Fang.
And he's stealing
those bifocals.
JOEL: They came to Earth
to steal bifocals.
TOM: Well, it's not his
prescription, I don't think.
CROW: I've gone blind.
I'm looking
at the back of my retinas.
-JOEL: No, it's just the movie.
-CROW: I'm blind.
TOM: The movie went blind.
CROW: Oh.
Wish I had gone blind.
[ Tom imitating Yoda ] Luke,
finish your training, you will.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
JOEL: Bambi, humans
are basically good.
TOM: Uh, check that.
CROW: You know, Mom,
you never hear the one
with your name on it.
MAN: See that?
Game around here isn't usually
at all nervous.
JOEL: My bloodlust
cannot be sated.
The light trembling of a fawn
as it lay dying in my arms,
you know.
MATT: Christ, you're beginning
to sound like Sam.
TOM: Son of Sam.
MAN: ...why or what.
But I got a funny feeling,
and I don't like it.
JOEL: I've gotta kill something
is what I gotta do.
-TOM: How about you?
-CROW: Gino Vannelli?
JOEL: Yee...
TOM: Needs a shave.
-JOEL: Ugh.
-TOM: Ooh. Right in the eye.
-ALL: Ooh.
-TOM: Whoa!
Whoo.
JOEL: The helpless cough of
a squirrel with a crushed face.
that's what life's all about.
MATT: What's the big hurry?
MAN: The big hurry's I wanna get
the hell out of here.
TOM: I'm doing a one-man show...
Leslie Nielson, Leslie Nielson,
Leslie Nielson.
MAN: I can tell you this,
something weird going on.
All right, look.
You stick around if you like.
I'm moving.
TOM: Movin' on.
CROW: Hey, you may want to wax
that bikini hair.
TOM: Oof!
TOM: Oh, you know,
even the movie "The Fog"
didn't have this much fog.
JOEL: Un-hunh.
You know, the entry wound
of a shot is a kill.
-TOM: Okay
-CROW: Please.
MATT: At least, we'd have
four walls and a roof.
MAN: And a jail cell tomorrow.
MATT: Oh, yeah,
guess you're right.
TOM: Eh, forget about that.
MAN: Give me some of that stuff.
TOM: Hi, God.
Look, there's Julie Andrews,
and she's on fire.
CROW: Good.
TOM: Sorry, Jules.
CROW: You know, this scene
didn't originally appear
in the movie,
but they, uh... they
restored it. Aren't you glad?
TOM: Oh, thank you, AMC.
Huh. Mm-hm.
CROW: Aah! It's the camera man.
He's looking
through the wrong lens.
JOEL: Oh, that comb... used to
belong to Keith Richards.
[ Crow retching ]
Look what I've got here,
Uncle Bill.
Huh, centipede.
It's a lithobius forficatus.
To me, it's a centipede.
It's always been called
a centipede.
CROW: He's a loving
and giving caregiver.
WOMAN:
What have you got there?
A lithobius forficatus.
Centipede.
Well, chuck
the filthy thing away.
It's for my insect collection.
Then, take it up to your room,
okay?
Can I go out and find
some more specimens?
Later. You've got to help
your uncle in the cellar.
Now, then,
finish your breakfast.
TOM: Aw.
CROW: Oops, wrong bowl.
[ Groaning ]
[ Lively music ]
TOM: 3M today.
A more vibrant future
for the plastic resin-based
industries!
Ah, finally a movie
for our generation.
Swingin'.
Whoo.
Get your bike ready,
leather jacket on
JOEL: Hey, it's Greg Brady!
TOM & CROW: Cool.
Let the engine go.
Oh, no, hold it. Hold it.
-It stinks.
-CROW: We agree.
Let's take it again
from the top.
CROW: Here's your coffee.
I made it special.
I'll be right over here. Bye.
MAN: You guys are
all over the place.
TOM: Yeah, you're up
in the mountains.
You're in the studio.
You're in a cave.
You're in a shotgun shack.
You're in another part
of the world.
You're on top
of Old Smokey there.
Huh. You're all over the place.
CROW: We're just as confused
as you are, folks.
TOM: Ah, the heck with this,
Norm.
Let's go down to the suburbs
and crash
through a school window.
CROW: Hey, okay.
Hey, you hear about Phil?
He got hit by a truck
last night.
TOM:
Ooh, down by the salt lick?
-CROW: Yeah.
-TOM: Oh, what a shame.
MAN: Ah, here they come.
JOEL: Walkin' down the street.
They get the funniest looks
from everyone they meet.
TOM: Wait, those aren't deer.
CROW: Well, let's shoot them.
They're not wearing orange.
JOEL: They're going to die
in that Samurai Jeep anyway.
[ Gears grinding ]
CROW: Uh, uh,
you're still in first.
CROW: No... Mo... You don't know
how to drive a stick, do you?
MAN: Oh, hell,
don't say they're going to
have problems, not now.
CROW: They're going to have
problems, not now.
MAN: Christ.
No. There they go.
They're okay.
Good riddance.
Now we can kill us some game
in peace and quiet.
TOM: Do you realize
what you just said?
[ Matt laughs ]
MATT: Or maybe just go and rest
in the cabin.
JOEL: Huzzah.
[ Tom laughing ]
MAN: I say we take a rest.
ALL: Aah!
...kick her into gear
Steady as she goes
Am I flying overdrive
-TOM: Flying over trout?
-MAN: Heading down the highway
TOM: Hey, you think the mike's
picking up their dancing?
All I wanna feel is the wind
in my eyes
CROW: Lyrics by Mrs. Johnson's
Kindergarten Class.
-TOM: Wind in my eyes?
-All systems ready to go
JOEL: All victims ready
to skull?
-MAN: Hear the engines roar now
-TOM: Idiot control now
Hear the engines roar now.
TOM: Idiot control...
Hey, Greg Louganis
is so talented.
JOEL: Cute, too.
TOM: Young Republicans...
They're so hip!
JOEL: This may...
might be Mike CurbCongregation's
best album ever!
BACKUP SINGERS:
Burning rubber tires
TOM: Whoo!
-That's nice.
-Now they got it together.
TOM: Oh, yeah, they got it
together now.
[ Tom laughing ]
CROW: Hmm, hmm, hmm,
ceiling needs painting.
WOMAN: He is really good.
Good? He's the best.
TOM: Oh, I could say...
JOEL: Uh, just leave it
like that.
Hear the engines roar now
ALL: Hear the young potato
ALL: Idiot control now
Hear the engines roar now
TOM:
Hideous control now
Hear the engines roar now
ALL:
Digging Minnie Pearl now
Hear the engines roar now
Wheels on fire
Burning rubber tires
TOM: Whoo!
Hear the engines roar now
TOM: Nice song, but I think
it needs a hook or something.
Hear the engines roar now
TOM: Get down, Crow.
CROW: I can't. Back up.
Hear the engines roar now
TOM: Whoo!
JOEL: If these guys
get any more soul,
we'll have to order out
for greens.
-Okay
-Hmm? Good.
[ Sighing ]
Well?
TOM: Hmm?
-It stinks.
-TOM: D'oh.
ALL: Whah, whah, whah.
Well, what's the matter with it?
Who knows?
It was great.
TOM: Hmm.
[ Sighs ]
BACKUP SINGER:
I hope you're joking.
I never joke about my living.
Well, I thought
it was great this time.
Great? Yeah.
Kathy was half-asleep,
and you, Tracy, you were
blasting out like a foghorn.
What's wrong with him, then?
Did he get up on the wrong side
of the bed?
-CROW: You should know.
-TOM: Hey, shh.
-And you.
-Me, what?
Come on, out with it.
You came in half a beat late.
JOEL: Ooh.
SINGER: What are you
talking about, Rick?
Back in a minute...
SINGER:
I came in half a beat late?
I'm not going to argue, Sharon.
You came in late.
Come on, Rick,
give me a break.
You're always early.
You're impossible to follow.
MAN: Yay. Fantastic, everybody.
JOEL: Hey, it's Andy Travis
from WKRP!
Gary's really excited
about this take.
Why don't you ask him?
-TOM: Hmm?
-Hmm?
Hey, guys, the fun's over.
Well, I still say
you were all fantastic. Really.
It's gonna be a hit for sure.
You wanna hear it again?
-ALL: No. No.
-That's okay, Gary.
It's been a long day.
We'll hear it on Monday.
Thanks.
Have a nice weekend.
CROW: But it's Wednesday.
TOM: Long weekend.
MAN: And now,
let's get out of here.
Let's get up
into those mountains
and breathe a little fresh air.
After the atmosphere in here,
it'll probably kill us.
MAN: Tracy,
go pick up the scores.
JOEL: And my leather clown suit.
-Me and my big mouth.
-Place is really great.
You'll love it up there.
Hey, Gary, how about it. Huh?
Sorry, honey.
Got a mess of work.
Oh, come on, Gary.
You'll have a wonderful time.
I'll belong to you,
soul and body.
CROW: No, I just ate.
Thanks.
GARY: I'm sorry, Tracy, it's
been a long week, and, well...
Okay, don't worry.
I get the message.
I know I'm not your type.
What the hell?
There's always Robert Redford.
TOM: Oh, we gotta go, guys.
-Come on, give me a break.
-TRACY: That's what I was doing.
CROW: Oh.
TRACY: Don't call us.
We'll call you.
JOEL: She should be more
accessible, you know?
-So long, super stud.
-TOM: Yeah.
All right, all right,
let's do it again.
You come in late, girls,
again... you're out.
All right?
All right, from the top.
[ Lively music plays ]
With a pickle mind
We kick the nipple beers
Steady as a goat
We're flying over trout
Ghetto down the highway
At the speed of light
All I wanna feel now
Is the wind in my eyes
Sack of monkeys
In my pocket
My sister's ready to go
Hear the engines roar now
Idiot control now
Hideous control now
Ninny on the road now
Minnie in control
Wheels on fire
Burning rubber tires
[ Gypsy mumbling ]
Whoo!
He's pretty good.
Good? He's the best.
Blurry jelly rolls now
Hiddy lets it go now
Needy inches bow down
Pitying a poor boy
Hear the engines roar
Bees on pie
Burning rubber tires
Whoo!
[ Sighing ]
Oh, great. Pretty good.
What do you think?
[ Pinging sound ]
It stinks.
-Mom...
-ALL: Hear the engines roar now
TOM: Woof. That was
a hot session, huh?
Oh, yeah.
RICK: Look, Sharon, honey,
I'm sorry.
I got all uptight.
TOM: D'oh.
RICK: This is important to me,
this LP, you know that.
Don't you?
Just forget it, will you?
You know
I didn't mean anything.
TOM: Ah, kiss me, you big lug.
TOM: Mm-mm.
TRACY: Hey, you got all weekend.
JOEL: Oh, that's right.
All for fun.
-TOM: Oh, that's sweet, huh?
-JOEL: Oh, neat. Let's go.
CROW: And they have Pringles.
TRACY: You think the weather's
going to hold?
TOM: No, I think it's
just going to stop.
Hey, where did you say
we were going?
-CROW: To hell.
-Cinder National Forest.
[ Sighs ]
It's a fantastic place.
So peaceful and so quiet.
Not a soul for miles, I suppose.
JOEL: I'm not bringing mine.
It's really out of the way.
Just a few rangers
and a lot of bears.
I guess I'll just have
to find a ranger
or a bear to sleep with, then.
TOM: What are you saying?
Ooh. Oh, sorry, wrong movie.
WOMAN: I'm cold.
I didn't bring my jacket.
CROW: Or your brain.
WOMAN: Do you mind if I put
on one of yours, Rick, darling?
CROW: Look, Pocahontas,
Rick's mine.
Somebody else needs warming up.
Who the hell is that?
Hi, y'all.
I'm Laura Stapleton.
JOEL: Maureen Stapleton?
-CROW: Naw.
-TOM: Looking good.
LAURA: Oh, Ricky,
you were wonderful.
Marvelous.
You were all great.
We're going to have
such fun this weekend.
-TOM: Uh-oh.
-Yeah, great fun.
TOM: Ooh.
-Sharon!
-What's got into that...?
-CROW: Girl.
-Are you all right, Rick?
CROW: All right in the bags?
S'all right.
LAURA: Open this door!
BRIAN: Who on Earth made you
invite her along?
-LAURA: What's going on?
-Forgot we met the other day.
I guess I must've told her
about the weekend by accident.
Yeah, accidently on purpose.
Never thought
she'd actually come.
Well, tell her to get lost.
I can't do that, can I?
Turns out she's the daughter
of one of the bosses here.
Makes her part of
the establishment, doesn't it?
And she happens
to like the way I perform.
Anyway, an artist has to think
about his public, doesn't he?
-TOM: Can't argue with that.
-JOEL: Ah, you make sense.
LAURA: What's going on?
Especially if your public
has boobs like that.
TOM: Uh, Joel, what are boobs?
JOEL: You know,
like Jethro Bodine?
TOM: Oh, boobs. Okay.
BRIAN: Sharon...
I think you're making
a mountain out of a molehill.
[ Tom clears throat ]
SHARON: Leave me alone.
I'm going home.
CROW: To change, I hope.
Believe me,
it's not what you think.
JOEL: It's what you're wearing.
SHARON: Of course not.
It's probably worse.
Anyway, that's it.
I'm finished with him.
Listen, Sharon.
Deep down, that guy is nuts
about you.
TOM: Mm-hm.
BRIAN: Making out with chicks
is part of his act as an artist.
JOEL: Hmm.
One today,
a different one tomorrow.
JOEL: See, cheating is hip.
BRIAN: Accept the fact.
And if you love him,
stand up and fight for him.
TOM: Enjoy being used.
BRIAN: There's no way
you lose out.
Especially against some idiot
like that.
So cool it. And relax.
Okay.
Brian's right, you know, Sharon.
-TOM: Mm-hm.
-Yes, isn't he always?
TOM: Mm-hm.
Why couldn't I fall in love
with him?
[ Laughing ]
-JOEL: And then they, oh...
-TOM: Come on, knuckleheads.
CROW: Still friends. Yeah.
Hey, try to be nice to your
boyfriend's girlfriend...
boyfriend.
TOM: There, that'll keep 'em.
-TOM: Uncle Bill?
-CROW: Jody?
-JOEL: Buffy?
-TOM: Mr. French?
JOEL: Mrs. Beasley?
-TOM: Chief?
-CROW: McCloud?
[ Tom laughing ]
-CROW: Boy, I hate Kenny.
-JOEL: Oh, that's not Kenny.
-JOEL: We like this kid.
-CROW: Oh.
CROW: Hey, it's Desi and Lucy
in "The Big, Big Trailer"!
[ Tom laughing ]
-JOEL: It's neat, huh?
-CROW: Yeah.
TOM: Is this white Reggae?
What should I do?
It's getting late
I'm feeling blue
JOEL: No, this is Morrissey.
CROW: Oh!
JOEL: I love it.
I sometimes think
It's one of the jokes
TOM: Ooga.
JOEL: It's a kooky radio,
isn't it?
[ Crow imitating Laura ]
Yeah, it goes in my ear.
[ Tom laughing ]
TOM: Boy, you know,
Ringo did some bad songs,
but this is really embarrassing.
JOEL: Yeah.
-What should I do?
-CROW: Retire.
She hasn't come
I'm feeling blue
JOEL: Hmm, this should fit
over my head.
That you will come
at the end
TOM: What?
Why you didn't call
and tell me
CROW: Give me that.
I'll scratch your eyes out.
SHARON: ...found a worse road
than this?
[ Laughing ]
JOEL: Fun. Levity.
TOM: Ah, the von Trapp Family
Singers on the road.
CROW: Hope they find some Nazis.
[ Tom laughing ]
TOM: Enjoy the good life
in retirement.
Scene back roads,
Morrissey songs
24 hours a day.
JOEL: And it really
came together
when Mom sang along.
You call me to tell me
you love me
You play the same game
again
What do you want from me?
[ Echoing ]
TOM: Oh, oh, Joel, Joel, Joel,
I'm tripping, tripping,
tripping.
-CROW: Talk him down, Joel.
-JOEL: It's just an Echoplex.
CROW: Talk him down.
-TOM: Oh.
-JOEL: It's the Echoplex, buddy.
TOM: Whew. I was worried.
CROW: Hey, look, we paid for
the van. We're gonna film it.
TOM: Paid for the song, too.
Gonna use it all.
JOEL: Oh, terrific, we're saved
by the Gates of Hell.
CROW: Hey, what is it
about the Gates of Hell
that compels people
to wander into 'em?
JOEL: It's because of Smuckers
raspberry preserves.
CROW: Man,
what's he going to do,
borrow a cup of sugar
from Satan?
JOEL: No, he's going to borrow
a cup
of Smuckers raspberry jam.
It's most like real fruit.
-TOM: Beastmaster?
-CROW: Ringo?
-JOEL: Axl?
-TOM & CROW: Sinead?
-TOM: Chief?
-CROW: McCloud?
[ Joel imitating boy ]
Wow, specimen jackpot.
TOM: Just, uh, put away
his Dinty Moore.
CROW: Oh, that'll go great
in his alien mutant hell beast
from space collection.
[ Gasps ]
TOM: It says, "Don't laugh.
It's paid for."
-JOEL: In Braille?
-TOM: Mm-hm.
BRIAN: Hey, one of you go
and help Rick collect firewood.
-JOEL: I'll go. I wanna die.
-[ Electronic chirping ]
TOM: Syntho birds.
-JOEL: Hmm.
-CROW: Hey, it's a Casio forest.
[ Electronic chirping
continues ]
JOEL: They parked
next to a data stream.
CROW: Hmm.
TOM: Hmm.
LAURA:
Rick? Ricky, wait for me.
Hey.
CROW: Hey, put the Casio
back in the van.
LAURA: I don't think the others
like me being here.
JOEL: Duh.
LAURA: They haven't said
a word to me.
-Ignore them, then.
-Oh, sure.
I would, but they dry-click
their revolvers at me.
RICK: What brought you here?
Me or them?
You, and you're right.
I don't care.
Kiss me, Ricky.
CROW: Where?
RICK: Not now. Later.
They're waiting for us.
I only asked you to kiss me.
-Don't you want to?
-CROW: No, I...
[ Muffled ]
CROW: You got my gum.
Rick!
Where are you, Rick?
CROW: Mmph... over here.
RICK: Hold on!
[ Sighs ]
I'm coming!
TOM: Mm-hm.
CROW: This is CNN.
WOMAN: Tommy.
JOEL: Have you been playing with
the gatekeeper again, Tommy?
-BRIAN: Well...
-TOM: Mmm.
If nothing else...
TOM: Oh, you know,
Steve tastes great.
-I wish everybody liked them.
-TOM: A little more pelvis?
What do you think, Laura, dear?
Mmm. Real good.
Hmm, you look
like you're enjoying it.
My mother's just the best darn
cook in the world.
She taught me to enjoy
good eating.
TOM: Mmm.
TRACY: Especially steaks, huh?
Not only.
All kinds of meat.
TOM: Pelvis.
SHARON: Sounds like a talented
lady, your mother.
TOM: My mother was a saint!
LAURA: ...you guys laughing
at me all the time.
JOEL: We're laughing
with you, dear heart...
TRACY: Oh, yeah, sure.
I know that you hate me.
You're jealous, aren't ya?
Because Ricky likes me.
Well, that's the way the cookie
crumbles, honey.
TOM: Ooh.
Tell her what we did
in the woods, Ricky.
She'd love to know.
Right, Sharon?
-[ Screams ]
-TOM: Coffee?
[ Laura huffs ]
TRACY: Laura!
-TOM: You forgot your breakfast!
TRACY: I think I better
go after her.
No, leave her alone
for a while.
Let her cool off.
CROW: Or get eaten by creatures.
TOM: Snap an ankle,
die of exposure.
BRIAN: You know, we have been
very hard on her.
CROW: Yeah, but it's a good
chance to thin out the cast.
[ Tom imitating weeping ]
I don't even like coffee.
[ Weeping ]
[ Tom slurping ]
JOEL: Only half a cup?
TOM: Mm-hm.
TOM: Don't you like
the rich taste?
TOM: Mmm.
-CROW: Dad?
-TOM: Mummy?
-Ricky? Is that you?
-CROW: Mr. Drysdale?
JOEL: Mr. Eddie's father?
LAURA: Don't play games with me,
please.
-CROW: Mr. Douglas.
-TOM: Mr. Haney.
-CROW: Lisa?
-TOM: Chief?
CROW: McCloud?
-Please come out.
-TOM: Shaking the trees.
Ricky, I'm frightened.
[ Gasps ]
Hey, look at the little birdie
I caught.
TOM: It's a girl, you idiot.
MAN: You know what, Matt?
You're a real blockhead.
You're just looking
to land up in jail.
JOEL: Come on. I can use you
in my act. Huzzah.
MAN: I ain't doing nothing.
You better run.
It's all forest that way.
She won't get far.
TOM: D'oh.
MATT: Come on.
CROW: And there,
on the handle, was...
You're not listening.
TRACY: Great weather
for a picnic.
I read it in my horoscope.
JOEL: My horoscope said you'd be
stalked by a leather mug maker
from a Renaissance Festival.
[ Panting ]
TOM: Run away!
MATT: Jesus, that little... Can
run a lot faster than I thought.
Yeah, well, you're a jerk.
TOM: Ooh, touche.
Very clever.
[ Gasps ]
-[ Creature growling ]
-[ Screams ]
TOM: Next week on Mannix.
TRACY: God, what was that?
CROW: Sounded like Laura
leaping to her death.
TRACY: Laura?
TOM: Jerk. You're a jerk.
Over there, jerk.
Come on, jerk.
Such a jerk.
SHARON: Come on.
JOEL: Wait, did we leave
the iron on?
BRIAN: Laura!
Where are you, Laura?
JOEL: Tell Laura I love her.
BRIAN: Laura!
TOM: Huh? Is your name Laura?
MAN: Nothing but trouble, Matt.
Let's get out of here fast.
JOEL: Bitty-bitty-bitty.
Wanna dance, Buck?
[ Tom laughing ]
TOM: Oh, it's Laura Palmer.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Soupy Sales.
-This way.
-CROW: What, do you smell her?
-TOM: Yeah, like a bloodhound.
-CROW: Yeah.
RICK: There she is.
TOM: Don't move.
We'll come down.
BRIAN: Laura!
-Laura!
-Jesus.
-She isn't dead, is she?
-I don't think so.
But she's sure in bad shape.
Get her legs.
CROW: Yeah, quick,
move her spine around a lot.
[ Making bone cracking noises ]
CROW: Dope.
Laura! Rick!
-TOM: Bosley?
-JOEL: Angels?
-TOM: Chief?
-CROW: McCloud?
KATHY: Daddy, where are you?
-TOM: Daddy?
-JOEL: Leviathan?
-TOM: Laverne?
-Where are they?
[ Crow imitating Squiggy ]
Hello!
SHARON: Over there.
[ Tom laughing ]
Oh, my God, what happened?
I don't know.
TOM: She's claiming
she's Anais Nin.
Things could get
kind of tricky now.
This place is going to be
swarming with rangers soon.
We better be on our way
out of here.
JOEL: We shouldn't have stole
that pic-a-nic basket.
MAN: We'll make for the old
hideout in the canyon, Big Bend.
-JOEL: Huzzah.
-Christ, that's miles away.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Come on.
TOM: Quick, let's fold her.
CROW: Well, I'm so glad they
turned her into a vegetable.
BRIAN: Give me one
of the blankets.
TOM: Uh, no, that's okay.
I'm not cold.
-CROW: It's for her.
-TOM: Oh.
TRACY: Here.
This'll warm her up.
TOM: Uh, no thanks.
I'm not thirsty.
-CROW: It's for her, for her.
-JOEL: For her.
-[ Chuckles ]
-TOM: Yes.
TOM: She obviously
doesn't need it.
-BRIAN: She's out cold.
-CROW: Yeah.
We've got to get her
to a hospital.
JOEL: Or a bar.
BRIAN: Hold on, Rick.
It's more than 50 miles.
In this weather, in these roads,
you wouldn't get very far.
We have to do something, Brian.
We can't just leave her.
It's my fault.
I forced her to run away.
Oh, Sharon, it wasn't you.
It was me.
-She'll be all right.
-JOEL: It's her fault.
RICK: Don't cry now.
What can we do, Brian?
CROW: Jam a sandwich
down her throat.
BRIAN:...refuge at Black Butte,
where there's a telephone,
and they can help us.
Then, let's get out things.
Come on.
TOM: Meanwhile,
in another movie...
Ah, patience, gentle viewer.
This'll all make sense
in the end.
-[ Chuckles ]
-TOM: Not.
CROW: I wonder when Flo
and Alice are going to get here.
TOM: Mel, at home.
[ Tom muffled ]
Let me out.
I said, let me out.
Ow, ow.
-CROW: Shave and a haircut?
-TOM: Two bits.
[ Heart beating ]
WOMAN: Tommy.
CROW: Just tending the incubus,
mother.
[ Cat meowing ]
Why haven't you gone
to bed yet?
I did, Mom,
but kitty was meowing,
and I thought
maybe he was hungry.
Oh, he's already eaten
at least three times today.
Then, he certainly
shouldn't have any more.
Okay, come on, into bed.
One of these days we're going
to have trouble with you two.
In you get.
TOM: And remember,
no wire hangers!
Settle down.
Now, go to sleep.
All right?
Yes, Mom.
Good night.
-TOM: Good night, mother.
-JOEL: Good night, John-boy.
-TOM: Good night, Hardcastle.
-JOEL: Good night, McCormick.
-TOM: Good night, Chief.
-CROW: Good night, McCloud.
[ Tom laughing ]
[ Cat meows ]
TOMMY: You all just wait
and see.
You're going to have
a new friend soon.
[ Chuckles ]
CROW: That's really great,
little kid.
TOM: Sad.
JOEL: Spends a lot of time
alone. Ugh.
Oh, he's trying
to hatch the egg.
What is he, Horton?
[ Tom laughing ]
[ Tom snores ]
TOM: Okay, so is this Movie A?
JOEL: Beats me.
[ Raspberries ]
TOM: Well, let's see.
The hunters are in Movie A.
The kid was in Movie B.
CROW: Ah, this is the Cowsills
part. This is Movie C....C.
JOEL: I shouldn't have had
so much coffee.
I'll be right back.
TOM: Ooh, enter the fog machine.
JOEL: Come on, honey.
You're gonna love it here.
RICK: Hello?
Anybody home?
What do you want
at this time of night?
We need help.
Well, go and find it
somewhere else.
Wait a minute, please.
Please, we need help.
What's going on, Bill?
Just a troublemaker.
-CROW: Nah, Jehovah Witnesses.
-Please, we need help.
Open the door, Bill.
Go on.
JOEL: Open the door.
RICK: Please, ma'am,
can we use your phone?
There's been an accident.
JOEL: She soiled herself.
-What kind of trouble?
-TOM: Oh, please.
-She fell.
-Bring her in.
-TOM: Accident.
-The telephone room.
Follow me.
TOM: Wakka-wakka?
RICK: This phone isn't working.
CROW: Give me that. I'll show
you how to use a prop phone.
-All right?
-Yeah, fine.
CROW: Eh, just a few more rooms,
and you'll be there.
Keep going.
TOM: Ooh, nice.
RICK: The line's dead.
There's been a rock fall.
The road's blocked.
The phone lines
are probably down, too.
JOEL: There's no way
out of this film.
BILL: God only knows
how you got this far.
Did you get through
to the hospital?
CROW: No, it's a prop phone.
RICK: No way.
The phone's screwed up.
That's all we need.
JOEL: Man, if it's not
one thing, it's another.
BRIAN: Surely there must be
some way of getting help.
TOM: Hey, life stinks, man.
Deal with it.
BILL: Not now, there ain't.
-You sure?
-Of course I am.
Come on.
I'll make you some coffee.
Don't worry.
She'll be all right.
TOM: Mm-hm.
MOM: With a good night's rest,
she'll be as right as rain
in the morning.
JOEL: Yeah, that's what cures
a crushed spine.
TOM: Uh-huh.
SHARON: What's going on?
Nothing.
The phone's not working.
The road back to town
is blocked.
Looks like there's
no way out of here.
But Laura needs help.
There must be some way.
Doesn't look like it.
Not in this bloody wilderness.
You and your out of the way
places.
-TOM: D'oh.
-SHARON: Come on now, Rick...
JOEL: Wow, a rock group
staying at my house?
Too much.
RICK: I know.
I'm not blaming you.
It'll all be all right.
I know where we can get help.
-Please, Mrs., uh...
-Stevens.
-Thank you.
-Molly Stevens.
-Tell us, Mrs. Stevens.
-JOEL: Molly Stevens.
Just a few miles from here
there's a forest ranger's cabin.
They've got a radio.
Then, what are we waiting for?
Not now.
You'll have to wait
for daylight.
At night you wouldn't make it.
Anyway, since it's springtime,
the rangers will be out
searching for poachers.
I'm right, Bill, aren't I?
CROW: Oh, yeah, I'll give you
that one.
MOLLY: Bill knows
where the patrols get to.
He'll take you there tomorrow.
Now you must get some rest.
It's no good worrying.
MOLLY: We've got plenty
of space here.
So as soon as you finish
your coffee,
I'll show you to your room.
BRIAN: You're being very kind.
TOM: Egg? Say, egg.
There's a lot of people here.
-TOM: Have ya... Huh?
-[ Tommy gasps ]
JOEL: Hey, uh...
TOM: Ooh, we gotta go.
[ Groaning ]
JOEL: Creamy living
chocolate center.
TOM: Ech!
[ Heart beating ]
Oh, hiya, Crow.
Oh, hi. Whatcha doin'?
Oh, we were just inspired
by the cool, new-age music
of this movie,
so we decided to use
the wall of keyboards
and make out own great
new new-age music.
You wanna help?
Sure.
Uh, what can I do?
Well, I could teach you
how to play the keyboards.
Will it take long?
No, of course not.
Come on over here.
Here, check this out.
Okay, put your hand... Come on,
put your hand over here.
-Okay.
-Put your finger down. See?
-Like that?
-Yeah.
-[ Note being played ]
-Ah.
Yeah, you got... you're playing
a new-age chord now, okay?
Hey.
Just like Yanni. All right, now,
put another finger down.
-Okay.
-See?
Now you're playing
a Yanni lick.
-Now, hold it down for an hour.
-Yeah.
Now hold it down till you get
a record contract
from Windham Hill.
-Oh, hey, cool.
-See?
Servo, check it out.
It's my new new-age Yanni lick.
Uh, Joel, hold on my new new-age
Yanni lick.
I've got to put
my sandwich down.
Okay. Got it.
This music's kind of dull,
isn't it?
Yeah, but it's a good way
to make a lot of money
without a big initial
investment.
[ Clears throat ]
Okay.
And now music
from some guys in space.
Tonight on music
from some guys in space,
more fine new new-age music
and sounds
from super progressive Bay Area
new-age keyboardist
Joel Robinson.
Joel will be accompanied
on the wall of keyboards
by veteran minimalist
Crow T. Robot.
We invite you to sit back
and enjoy
more repetitive new-age music
as we cruise the space ways.
Come along, fellow travelers,
and enjoy music
from some guys in space.
[ Alarm buzzing ]
Hey, we got movie sign,
you guys.
It's movie sign, next time
on Emergency 911.
Tom, you're stuck
in Shatner mode.
A duck with an arrow
through its neck.
Come on, man, snap out of it.
-Crow, wake up!
-Movie sign!
What?
[ All screaming ]
When I get a hold of that Sam,
I swear I'll kill him.
Standing us up here like this.
Oh, it's not so bad.
There's a connection I know
who'll give us at least,
I'd say...
TOM: You awake, Crow?
-...3,000 bucks for this lot.
-CROW: Yeah.
[ Crow sighs ]
How are we supposed
to get back to tow, huh?
On foot?
TOM: Wait a minute, I'm...
-[ Tom exhales ]
-TOM: Yep.
[ Sighs ]
MAN: It wouldn't be
the first time.
[ Tom chuckles ]
Why don't we take
the kids camper?
Are you crazy?
JOEL: Uh, can I think about it?
MAN: Haven't you screwed things
up enough already? Huh?
CROW: Well, he did write
the script.
JOEL: Huzzah.
MATT: What was that noise?
Maybe it's the rangers.
JOEL: Hey, Boo-Boo.
TOM: Eww.
Mm-hm.
MATT: What on Earth is that?
Looks like a cross
between a pig and a bear.
-CROW: A pear?
-My god it's ugly.
JOEL: Hey, you're no prize
yourself, Dan Folgelberg.
[ Tom laughing ]
Be careful.
It could be dangerous.
[ Cocks gun ]
Ah, it may be ugly, but it
appears harmless enough.
JOEL: Hey, it's
Mr. Snuffleupagus.
-TOM: Cute:
-CROW: I see...
MATT: Sure is a strange bird.
Think it could be
worth something?
-TOM: Queer kind of duck.
-MAN: Yeah, maybe.
-TOM: Maybe.
-Keep him busy.
-TOM: Keep him busy?
-Hey, uh, enjoying yourself?
Take a little night stroll?
Trouble is, the weather's
a little bit rough for that.
MATT: Isn't it?
CROW: Stop the inane
conversation.
MAN: Go on talking.
JOEL: You live around here much?
MATT: Eh, you must be hungry,
huh?
Have some.
CROW: It's one of you,
only gamier.
-TOM: Eww.
-MATT: It won't hurt ya.
-JOEL: So you like Chinese food?
-Don't be afraid. Come on.
MATT: Help yourself.
-JOEL: Huh?
-TOM: Mongolian barbecue?
-JOEL: Ha.
-TOM: Oh.
MAN: Matt, come on!
Give me a hand!
CROW: Get the drawn butter.
MAN: Christ, he's strong.
I can't... I can't hold him.
[ Screams ]
TOM: Alf, no! No, Alf!
[ Creature grunts ]
TOM: Ooh.
Big mistake.
CROW: Hey, that long nose must
be handy in hard-to-reach areas.
[ Tom laughing ]
[ Tom humming ]
TOM: Just pad out the scene here
a little bit.
[ Humming ]
JOEL: Hey, what gives?
I'm on the milk carton.
TOM: Hmm.
TOMMY: You're hungry again.
Aren't you?
There's no need to worry,
Trumpy.
You like that name.
Don't you, Trumpy?
-CROW: I prefer Milky Bear.
-TOMMY: I'm your friend.
TOMMY: And I won't let
anyone hurt you.
JOEL: I named you
after Donald Trump.
Trumpy.
Hello.
[ Crow imitating Trumpy ]
Hey, look.
Look what I got for you.
TOM: Mucus.
TOMMY: Oh, boy. You sure are
greedy. Aren't you?
TOM: Mm-hm.
TOMMY: Wow, if you keep drinking
milk like that,
you're going to grow really
big and strong.
Then we can play together.
You know what playing is,
Trumpy?
CROW: Yes, it's where
I break you in half.
TOMMY: No? I'll teach you.
We're going to have such fun.
TOM: Foreigner.
Uh, meanwhile in Movie C.
CROW: Uh, I think
this is Movie D.
-TOM: Oh.
-CROW: D for dumb.
[ Tom chuckling ]
TOM: Okay.
[ Gasps ]
JOEL: Oh, great.
TOMMY: Oh, boy,
how you've grown.
JOEL: Yeah, during the cutaway
anything's possible.
TOMMY: Keep growing like that,
and you won't fit any clothes.
Then what are we going to do?
Tommy, come on down
and eat your breakfast.
You've got to hide.
[ Belches ]
You understand?
You've got to hide.
Tommy, did you hear me?
TOM: Can you feel me near you?
Oh, what a nightmare.
Ooh, I dreamt I was
a crappy actress
in a horrible monster... film.
Hey, wait a minute.
JOEL: Oh, no, she really does
have combination skin.
CROW: Eww.
JOEL: Oh. Oh, my goodness.
CROW: Oh, bad. Big bad...
Big bad thing.
Help, everyone. Big bad.
SHARON: Rick!
JOEL: Hurry.
Big sale on flannel.
JOEL: Everyone, come on.
TOM: Flannel?
Did she say, "Flannel"?
JOEL: Here,
drink this coffee, kid.
CROW: Hmm.
Oh, he's stealing
all the Nerf toast.
[ Gasps ]
TOM: Uh, hello, remember us,
the audience?
Uh, could we see, please?
JOEL: I think her perm
didn't take.
CROW: Eww.
-[ Crying ]
-TOM: Aw!
CROW: Well, come on,
your breakfast is getting cold,
and she's not getting
any warmer.
[ Crying continues ]
That means more oatmeal
for everyone.
TOM: Right.
TOMMY: What happened, Mommy?
It's nothing to do with you,
dear.
TOM: Go play with your tripping
hell beast, darling.
MOLLY: But I don't want you
coming in here, understand?
Have you finished
your breakfast?
Then, you know
what you have to do now.
Run along.
[ Cat meows ]
[ Singing ]
CROW: Mmm. Delicious kitty.
Oh. Ouch.
Ooh, kitty's like a potato.
[ Birds chirping ]
CROW: Oh, so nice.
Oh, where do I start?
It all looks so good.
Little winged potatoes.
Ouch, that's my snout.
Ow, let go.
Hmm.
This potato's got big ears.
Yes.
TOM: Mm-hm.
CROW: It's a whole buffet.
New potatoes, hmm.
-TOM: Whoa!
-CROW: Aah!
TOM: Oh, it's a rogue robot.
He's got the mange.
He's gone rogue.
We're gonna have to kill him.
Speak to me, boy.
[ Rattling ]
TOM: Uh-oh.
CROW: Ah, never seen one
do that before.
Whoa!
TOM: Ooh, never seen one
do that before.
JOEL: Oh, that's no good.
Un-uh.
[ Humming ]
CROW: He's going to have
to house train 'em.
He can't just keep hauling
that stuff out.
TOMMY: I told you to stay
out of sight.
Nobody must see you.
TOM: He doesn't speak
your language, dickweed.
TOMMY: If you want to stay
with me,
you've got to do
what I tell you.
CROW: I don't think so.
TOMMY: You don't want them
to separate us, do you?
JOEL: Carbon scoring
all over my droid.
TOMMY: I've brought you
something special to eat.
Are you hungry now, Trumpy?
CROW: Yes.
TOM: Ooh, won't peanuts get
caught in his snout?
CROW: Oh, little potatoes.
[ Slurping noise ]
-TOM: Ooh.
-JOEL: Yeah.
CROW: Now you try.
TOMMY: Do you want some more?
JOEL: Oh, wait. Let me get
the attachments.
You can do the couch.
TOMMY: You know,
sooner or later,
Mommy's going to notice
all this food disappearing.
Then, you'll have to kill her.
These we'll put away
for later.
CROW: No, more.
Now we can play.
-CROW: Like hell. More food.
-You know how to play, Trumpy?
What do you know?
CROW: Food, eating, the theater.
TOMMY: Nothing?
JOEL: Boy, I sure hope Trumpy
doesn't sneeze
and pistol-whip that kid
with peanuts.
CROW: Wow,
never thought about that.
TOMMY: I'll show you how to do
a jigsaw, okay?
-TOM: Oh, that's exciting.
-Here, come on.
TOM: Pente, the ancient game
of stones.
Hmm?
You see?
The pieces go together.
No, no, no,
start with the corner pieces.
JOEL: Oh, if only this film
were so lucky.
TOMMY: You understand?
It's easy.
JOEL: Why are you looking at me
like that, Trumpy?
TOMMY: Well, Trumpy, you get it?
CROW: No.
TOMMY: No, hmm?
Well, let's try another game.
Cheating. You must
teach me one day.
All right. Now, then,
look at me.
CROW: Can I eat it?
It looks so good.
Pay attention and repeat
what I do.
TOM: Like a potato?
Uh, no, wait, wait.
Let me try again.
-TOMMY: Are you watching?
-TOM: Damn.
TOM: No, no, that's not...
There, okay.
[ Beeping ]
TOM: Yeah, that's it.
[ Beeping continues ]
TOM: Oh, he stinks.
JOEL: Not very good. Is he?
CROW: Un-uh.
TOM: Yeah, that's great.
Give me that.
There, it's your turn.
-[ Game playing melody ]
-TOM: Huh?
-CROW: Huh?
-TOM: Oh, it's kooky.
-CROW: Hey.
-Gee.
JOEL: Trumpy, you can do
stupid things.
Isn't this Gary Numan
and the Tubeway Army?
-TOM: Yep.
-ALL: In cars
JOEL: In cars
TOM: In trucks
[ Tom laughing ]
CROW: I got a kooky idea
for a new song.
TRACY: And now what are
we going to do?
Find the rangers and tell them
what's happened to you.
It's a bit late.
It's more important now
than ever before.
You saw them,
those marks on her face.
-TOM: Oh.
-It's horrible.
TOM: Oh, just go out
and get yourself a new pair
of disco camping boots
there, dear.
MOLLY: Warm up the Jeep.
Molly, the road is
in a terrible condition.
Come on, Bill.
If anyone can get through,
you can.
We've got to try.
Listen, I'll come with you.
I'll just get...
No, I'll go.
You stay with Sharon.
Why don't we all go
in the camper?
-JOEL: Oh, just go! Somebody.
-TOM: Come on.
MOLLY: What about the phone,
then?
Lines are still down.
I just tried it.
Well, that's it.
What are we gonna do?
Find the rangers?
CROW:
Pepperidge Farm remembers.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
TOM: Mm, mm, mm, mm.
You're a good kid.
JOEL: Remind me
to use you later.
CROW: Hope she doesn't miss
her Josie and the Pussycats
audition.
[ Engine starting ]
JOEL: You know,
I never liked him.
TOM: Aloha.
Auf wiedersehen.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
TOM: Mm-hm.
Okay, you've drawn Siegfried.
Now, where's Roy?
TOMMY: That's my mommy.
-CROW: Aah!
-TOM: Ooh.
TOMMY: Do you have a mommy?
CROW: He was born of an omelet.
Of course not.
TOMMY: You don't know?
TOMMY: Does she look like this?
-CROW: Ooh.
-TOM: No, no.
TOMMY: Or like this?
TOM: Any distinguishing marks
or scars?
Where is she, then?
CROW: Where did he learn
English?
TOMMY: Oh, she's in a tree.
JOEL: Uh, I can tell by
the expression on your face
that you loved her so, Trumpy.
TOM: What,
she's from Rand McNally?
TOMMY: On a star?
CROW: Can she carry moonbeams
home in a jar?
TOMMY: Wow!
With this you can see
the stars.
You want to look?
TOM: This kid sounds
like Georgette.
JOEL: Yeah.
CROW: Kitty.
JOEL: Oh, they got "Wild
Kingdom" on that telescope.
TOM: Cool.
[ Drums beating ]
JOEL: Mm-hm.
And drums, too?
TOMMY: You can do magic things.
CROW: It's called evil, kid.
TOM: He's got his high beams on.
Hmm?
JOEL: He's got Bette Davis eyes.
[ Tom laughs ]
CROW: Orphan Annie eyes.
JOEL: Oh, great,
now we're in "Gumby".
TOM: Whoo!
CROW: I'm going to go walk
through a book.
TOM: Ooh, it's
supercalafragilistic-
expialidocious.
[ Tom giggles ]
D'oh.
CROW: I love this.
It's so spontaneous.
-TOM: Whoo!
-[ Crow laughs ]
JOEL: Oh, wow, we're in
"Pee-Wee's Playhouse" now.
CROW: Oh, yuck.
CROW: It's a Peter Gabriel
video.
TOM: Yeah, somebody hit that kid
in the head with a...
sledge hammer.
[ Laughing ]
JOEL: Wow. Oh, this alien
makes student films, huh?
TOM: What, did he come
from Planet Goofball?
Did he come here
in a little clown car?
Criminy.
JOEL: Great, now he can remake
"Rudolph's Shiny New Year."
[ Tom chuckling ]
TOM: Poor rabbit.
CROW: Poor us.
TOMMY: Trumpy?
Where are you?
CROW: Get me!
I'm Lionel Richie!
JOEL: That's not right.
TOMMY: Trumpy.
TOM: Huh?
TOMMY: Hey, come back down.
TOM: Really looked
like a ceiling. Didn't it?
Oh, fun.
CROW: Whew!
MOLLY: Tommy,
what are you doing?
JOEL: It's just my Spike Jones
album, Mom!
TOM: Tommy, now,
you quit warping time and space
this instant.
MOLLY: Tommy.
Did you hear me, Tommy?
-Come on, quickly.
-CROW: Busted.
Hide in there.
[ Imitating Trumpy ]
Are you okay?
TOMMY: Yes, Mom.
What's going on here?
-Little Joe got out.
-What?
My hamster Joe escaped.
Well, try and be a little more
careful.
I told you a thousand times,
I don't want you...
TOM: I'd like some
breakfast please.
...turning this house
into a zoo.
And stop fidgeting around
like that.
Yes, Mommy.
All right. Now, come downstairs
with me and behave yourself.
I've got enough problems.
TOM: Make that three
hard-boiled eggs.
CROW: I've got to get a series.
JOEL: Now, do you think
those are blue contacts,
or are his eyes naturally
that color?
TOM: Oh, you mean,
like Whoopi Goldberg?
JOEL: Yeah.
[ Tom laughs ]
TOM: Get my head caught
in the snout there.
CROW: Now to find a herd
of cattle to drain dry.
TOM: Meanwhile in a winter movie
somewhere.
JOEL: Gosh, that last scene
was goofy.
I'm glad we weren't in it.
BILL: Ah, sometimes there is.
I thought hunting
wasn't allowed around here.
It's not.
Why are you carrying this rifle,
then?
TOM: For you.
Well, if that friend of yours
Laura had carried one,
she'd still be alive.
JOEL: Hurts.
TOM: Ooh.
CROW: Hey, it's a matching shirt
and sofa set.
TOM: Hi, gang.
[ Tom humming ]
TOM: Hmm, not bad.
Oh, the new Vogue is here.
TRACY: Molly,
is the television working?
I think so, yes.
Well, at least we won't miss
"Dallas" this week.
CROW: Oh great,
your friend just died,
and you're gonna watch "Dallas"?
TOM: Tsst.
KATHY: Tracy, how can you kid
around like this,
things being the way they are?
TOM: Thank you.
TRACY: Because if I didn't,
I'd be in hysterics.
-It doesn't work.
-JOEL: I'm in hysterics!
That's strange.
It was working yesterday.
JOEL: I rerouted the power
into Trumpy.
The radio makes
a funny noise, too.
TOM: Uh, that's called music.
TOMMY: Can I go back to my room,
Mommy?
Yes, you can.
CROW: For the rest of your life.
KATHY: How is Sharon?
She's gone to bed.
She was shattered.
-JOEL: This town's in tatters.
-TOM: Shadoobie.
TRACY: So peaceful, so quiet.
[ Tracy chuckles ]
[ Tom chuckles like Tracy ]
TOMMY: Trumpy.
[ Joel makes snarling noise ]
[ Tom chuckles ]
TOM: Face it, kid.
Trumpy never loved you.
Boo! Gotcha!
[ Tom laughs ]
TOMMY: Trumpy, where are you?
JOEL: Were ties ever that wide?
-Ah.
-TOM: Ah.
CROW: All right.
S'all right.
JOEL: Nothin'
CROW: Hmm.
[ Cat meows ]
TOMMY: Have you seen Trumpy?
JOEL: He tried to eat me.
He's evil.
TOM: Forget you.
Boo!
[ Tom laughs ]
-TOM: Cujo?
-JOEL: Evil one?
-JOEL: Supreme being?
-CROW: Alf?
-TOM: Chief?
-CROW: McCloud?
TOMMY: Trumpy, come on.
Where are you?
CROW: He seeks him here.
He seeks him there.
He seeks that rascal
everywhere.
TOM: Ah, don't worry about him.
He's moody and introspective.
He's in a corner reading
"Swimming to Cambodia".
CROW: Hmm.
TOMMY: Trumpy, are you in here?
JOEL: This is, like, the house
of a million foyers.
[ Suspenseful ]
TOM: Dum, dum
CROW: Dad?
TOM: Dum
-CROW: Dad?
-TOM: Dum
TOM: Don't go
into the dining room.
JOEL: Here's Tommy!
TOMMY: Trumpy.
JOEL: Sounds like music
from the "High Plains Drifter",
doesn't it?
-TOM: Mm-hm.
-CROW: Yeah.
TOM: Has a Sergio Leone
feel to it.
CROW: Bad choice.
JOEL: Oh, those are ready
to pop, I would say.
[ Imitating grinding noise ]
TOM: Oh, thank goodness
it's summer again.
We've been driving for months.
BILL: Doesn't look
like anybody's in.
But how can you tell
from here?
TOM: Oh, why don't you just go
up to the door?
You drove two seasons
to get here.
For crying out loud.
CROW: Boy,
he's really burning oil.
TOM: Mm-hm.
JOEL: I'm going to let this
do the talking.
BILL: Charley? Jack?
Is anyone there?
JOEL: He knows them,
and he's bringing a gun?
TOM: Oh,
it's a little practical joke.
He kicks open the door
and plugs them with 30 rounds.
It's kind of an inside family
thing, you know.
CROW: Housewarming gift.
TOM: Mm-hm.
-JOEL: Aah!
-TOM: Ooh.
JOEL: Oh, it's that guy.
-What do you think you're...?
-Shh.
JOEL: Hey, Bill, are those
Haggar slacks you're wearing?
Farah?
Dad N' Lad?
The Guys?
[ Tom chuckling ]
CROW: Watch this.
Little joke.
CROW: Hi! We're the cast
from "Straw Dogs".
[ Crow laughing uneasily ]
TOM: Sometimes it works.
TOM: Watchtower!
Oh, just kidding.
[ Tom & Crow chuckle ]
TOM: That thing in the magazine.
BRIAN: What the hell
happened here?
TOM: Hmm.
JOEL: Hmm.
BILL: The radio's not working.
CROW: Oh, nuts! I wanted
to hear Shadoe Stevens.
BILL: Charley? Jack?
JOEL: Biff? Happy? Anybody?
BRIAN: You think they're
in the other roo...
After all this shouting,
I sure hope not.
JOEL: Horse poster compliments
Dynamite magazine. For teens.
CROW: Turkey legs in the...
[ Groans ]
BRIAN: He's dead, I think.
TOM: His last words were,
"Huzzah!"
BILL: What's that?
Same mark that... Laura had.
Is he one of the rangers?
JOEL: No, but we could dress him
like a ranger.
BILL: No, he's a poacher,
name of Matt Collins.
Let's get the hell
out of here.
I don't know.
[ Growling ]
BILL: Look out! Jesus!
CROW: Aah!
CROW: Alf's back,
and this time it's personal.
[ Tom chuckling ]
TOM: Ooh, Reagan's next.
CROW: Pepperidge Farm remembers!
Pepperidge Farm remembers!
The heck with it.
I'm getting out of here!
Crackers or no!
TOM: That is the frumpiest...
monster I've ever seen.
JOEL: Yep.
CROW: Hey, wait!
You got coupons comin'.
JOEL: No hitchhikers.
It's company policy.
TOM: Ooh.
Ah, enough
of that exciting stuff.
Meanwhile, in still yet
another movie.
[ Sighs ]
[ Tom hiccups ]
CROW: What the...?
MOLLY: You're a good cook,
Tracy.
Unusual with girls today.
Well, my mother taught me.
She always said that men
like you for your meat
and after, your dessert.
[ Tom groans ]
You know how it is.
If you haven't got a pretty face
to begin with,
there's nothing you can do.
JOEL: Well, I think your mother
had a filthy mouth.
TRACY:...including
the 7-day beauty plan.
TOM: Didn't work.
MOLLY: Come on.
It's not that bad.
You've got a lot
of good points.
Yeah, and I know
the ones men like.
These and this.
But you're very intelligent.
Yeah, I don't know what
threatens the guys more...
my face or my intelligence.
CROW: Yeah, E=mc2.
TRACY: Hey, I'm getting a bit
worried about Brian and Bill.
They've been gone now
for hours.
Oh, maybe they got held up.
Or couldn't find the rangers.
Oh, yeah, these rangers.
JOEL: Down, girl.
Heel. Take it easy.
TRACY: All right, Molly.
I know.
Just in case, however,
I'm going to get my makeup
from the camper.
-I forgot it last night.
-TOM: Take a cold shower.
Now, what's going on, Tommy?
You've been running
in and out all day.
What are you looking for?
Nothing. Just getting
some water for Joe.
-Oh.
-Joe?
Are you hiding a man somewhere
in this house?
Joe is Tommy's hamster, Tracy.
-Oh, what a shame.
-TOM: Geez, Tracy, stay away
from the kid's animals.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
[ Tom humming ]
[ Crow whistles ]
CROW: Ba-dump-a-dee
Time to Armor All my pants.
JOEL: Oh, this is great.
He's gonna do
that Bob Newhart routine.
-[ Tom chuckles ]
-TOM: Love that.
JOEL: Uh, Abner? Yeah, hello.
Still isn't working.
Where the hell have Brian
and that old geezer got to?
It's been seven hours
since they left.
Didn't have that far to go.
Maybe something
happened to them.
Wouldn't surprise me.
Bill's as thick as two planks.
-CROW: Is he green-sheeted?
-How are Sharon and Kathy?
They took sleeping pills
and went to bed.
They were absolutely scared
out of their wits.
Maybe you should do the same.
[ Mocking ] TOM: Maybe you
should do the same.
[ Thunder distantly rumbles ]
JOEL: Trumpy? I brought you
a cup of treacle.
TOMMY: Trumpy.
-TOM: Aww.
-Where are you hiding?
Hey, she's got her L.L. Bean
disco survival boots on.
TOM: Survive in style.
JOEL: Trumpy, bring me the girl.
I desire to be read to.
[ Drums ]
TOM: Neil Peart on drums.
CROW: Hey, it's Craig Wasson,
all of a sudden.
JOEL: Now Trumpy and I will do
my version of "Rear Window".
[ Woman screams ]
TOM: I think she found Trumpy.
ALL: Whah, whah, whah.
[ Woman groans ]
CROW: Hey, this is not healthy
for a little boy.
I can't watch.
[ Groans continue ]
JOEL: Trumpy, no.
I told you no.
TOMMY: Trumpy.
TOM: When good pets do bad
things, on "A Current Affair".
JOEL: That was neat.
[ Gasps ]
JOEL: Trumpy, we hardly knew ye.
[ Tom coughs ]
TOM: Put out the van.
Oh, so people are being
methodically killed
by the Banana Splits.
JOEL: There goes Drooper.
-JOEL: Fleegle.
-TOM: Snork.
[ Gunshot ]
TOM: Mm-hm.
-Oh, my God.
-Bill.
-BILL: So what, she's dead?
-RICK: Yeah, she is.
What the hell's going on?
-It was a damned animal.
-What animal?
-CROW: The damned one.
- Where's Brian?
He's dead.
Dead? Where?
Back at the hut.
CROW: Oh, take the Baretta
hat off, old man.
TOM: Aww.
[ Tom chuckles ]
TOM: Faster, Trumpy, kill, kill.
RICK: What the hell?
What's happening?
Answer me, you goat.
What is this?
[ Tom imitates a goat ] What
have you done, you old bastard?
Stop it! Have you both
gone crazy?
I want to know who it was killed
Brian and Tracy and why.
-I told you.
-TOM: We have to go.
-JOEL: Oh.
-It was that weird animal.
And if we stay here,
it'll kill us all.
What sort of fairy tale
is this?
Oh, listen, Rick.
We'll sort this out later.
Now help Bill carry Tracy
inside.
Bill.
You are magic.
Aren't you, Trumpy?
[ Circus music ]
Trumpy, you come down.
[ Screaming ]
[ Carnival music plays ]
I can't bring 'em down.
I don't know how it works.
I'm stuck! I'm stuck!
Oh, we got commercial sign!
[ Carnival music
continues playing ]
I really don't know
what kind of animal it was.
All I know is I was very lucky.
Whatever it is, it's already
killed four people.
And maybe more.
Where are you going, Rick?
-To wake up the girls.
-Why?
So we can get out of here.
I ain't hanging about to find
out who's next for the chop.
-You can't leave now.
-No? Why not?
TOM: I made quiche.
BILL: It's getting dark,
'cause the road's blocked,
because that thing,
that murderous animal
is maybe waiting for us.
CROW: Yeah, but give me
a good reason.
MOLLY: He's right, you know.
We better wait till morning.
Listen, I'm sick and tired
of hearing the same old story.
JOEL: I'm sick and tired
of being I'm sick and tired.
How can you say that, Rick?
Well, I'm getting out of here,
and if I were you,
I'd take the kid and leave.
TOM: Kid? What kid?
Oh, my God.
CROW: Don't start with me,
Martha.
BILL: If you've got a bit
of sense, then, you'll stay.
He's right, Rick.
He knows the forest.
I'd better make sure
that all the doors and windows
are bolted.
JOEL: Now for some peach
cobbler.
TOM: Oh, George, get me a drink.
Boo? Boo Radley?
CROW: Dark One? Beelzebub?
-JOEL: Chief?
-CROW: McCloud?
[ Tom laughing ]
CROW: Trumpage! Trumpazoid!
The Trumpmonster!
TOM: Trumparino!
Stretching the premise.
[ Trumpy yelling ]
JOEL: He knocked his block off,
but you can press it
back down again
with the Rock 'Em Sock 'Em
Robots! By Marx.
TOM: So, what can I get ya?
Ouzo, vodka, Sambuca, Pernod,
Frangelico, Blue Curacao,
Glenmorangie, B&B, Hennessy,
Tanqueray,
hundred-year-old brandy?
RICK: I've never needed
a gun to defend myself.
Yeah, right.
You probably pay others
to defend you.
TOM: No, I use a woman
as a shield.
What the hell
are you doing?
CROW: Beer and a shot,
like you said.
TOM: All right, all right,
I'll get the smoky
12-year-old scotch.
Okay.
What are you doing?
JOEL: He shot my Jim Beam
pheasant decanter!
He's gone crazy.
Look.
What is it with you two?
Haven't we got enough trouble?
I don't like anyone bugging me.
TOM: Yeah.
[ Knocking on door ]
TOMMY: Mommy, open the door.
Let me in.
It's Tommy.
TOM: I'll get him.
[ Imitates gun cocking ]
CROW: Tommy, throw open the door
and say "pull".
[ Crow giggling ]
[ Tom chuckling ]
MOLLY: Where did you spring
from?
JOEL: From your loins, Mommy.
Didn't I tell you to stay
in your room?
I went to pick some plants
for all...
Plants for all your animals,
I suppose, right?
That's it. Out they're going
to go in the morning.
Now, get to your room and
don't move till I tell you to.
TOM: Ooh.
Wake up, Kathy.
TOM: I think I got something
to say to you.
SHARON: I heard a shot.
Shot?
You must've been dreaming.
-Wake up.
-What time is it?
TOM: You know, I'm starting
not to believe this movie.
I believed it when Alf
went on the killing spree,
but now... I don't know.
I don't know. I just hear voices
from downstairs.
Wow. Those pills
sure are strong.
I'm going to take a shower
and try to wake myself up.
-That's a good idea.
-TOM: Say.
But don't take too long.
TOM: Oh.
CROW: Honey, I'm home.
Oh, I'm a little kid.
JOEL: Nosy?
TOM: Chirpy?
CROW: Ratboy? Sondra Locke?
-TOM: Chief?
-CROW: McCloud?
JOEL: Now, for my
wonderful experiment
of joining a duck's body
to a rabbit's head.
There.
[ Tom humming ]
TOM:
I'm all alone in the world
Hey, the evil one's back.
-TOMMY: Trumpy.
-TOM: Yay!
CROW: Hey, it's like that scene
in "Mac and Me"
when Mac came back to life!
TOMMY: No, stay there.
Why did you kill that girl?
Why did you do that?
Now I can't be
your friend anymore.
-TOM: Bad hell beast.
-CROW: Did it for the kicks.
TOMMY: You're naughty, Trumpy.
Very naughty.
JOEL: Where have you been,
young man?
This is not a hotel.
TOMMY: You wouldn't kill me,
would you?
[ Tom laughs ]
Trumpy, was it you?
TOM: I like you, Tommy.
I'll kill you last.
TOMMY: Are you saying
there's another one?
Listen, Trumpy.
Uncle Bill wants to kill you.
JOEL: My advice...
don't let him.
JOEL: Looks real bad for you,
man.
What can we do?
TOM: Oh, you could put on a play
in the backyard.
Trumpy could play Cyrano.
TOMMY: You can't stay here
anymore.
And I don't want you to go.
Listen. We'll go together
and hide in the woods.
No, wait here.
I'll find you a disguise.
CROW: What do you think he's
going to dress him up as...
Drew Barrymore?
-JOEL: Henry Thomas he's not.
-No.
TOM: Oh, suddenly I feel like
someone should be reading
a Robert Frost poem.
"Something there is that doesn't
love a crummy monster film."
That's from "Mending Monster
Film" by Robert Frost.
-CROW: Neat.
-TOM: Mm-hm.
CROW: Mint julep?
[ Belches ]
TOM: Uh, no thanks. I've had 12.
JOEL: Sure hope the liquor
holds out.
TOM: I don't know.
[ Joel humming ]
JOEL: I'm in the shower
Nothing will happen to me
[ Imitating mother from Psycho ]
CROW: Norman? Norman?
Important phone call!
TOM: I wonder if Bobby likes me.
I like him.
JOEL: Check it out.
Product placement right there.
Yep.
[ Tom chuckling ]
TOM: "Die Hard 2" this is not.
CROW: Hmm... Coke, Sprite,
Pepto-Bismol,
United Airlines,
Steve Guttenberg.
TOM: Uh-huh.
There. Now you look like Admiral
Peary playing the Elephant Man.
TOMMY: Hold on a minute.
I'll go and investigate.
JOEL: Trumpy felt scarred
by his ugly hillbilly... nose.
CROW: Looks like a baseball bat
from Alaska.
TOM: Oh, Velvet Hammer?
Harvey Wallbanger?
Pink Squirrel? Little hair
of the alien that bit ya?
[ Tom chuckles ]
[ Crow hums ]
CROW: I'm naked and all alone
in the shower.
I'm totally vulnerable
and somebody could kill me.
[ Continues to hum ]
TOM: It's probably likely
at this point in the film.
CROW: My brain fell out.
JOEL: Say, I look just like fog.
TOM: Hmm?
JOEL: Oh.
[ Crow imitating squeaking ]
CROW: You need a protein rinse.
And you have dandruff.
TOM: Uh, honey...
[ Kathy screams ]
CROW: What? What, what?
What?
[ Screaming continues ]
TOM: Wait! Wait, I made you
a special drink.
Don't forget the coaster!
SHARON: Rick!
Brian!
TOM: Somebody!
RICK: Kathy!
[ Kathy screams ]
TOM: Ooh.
CROW: Don't look at me
without makeup.
-TOM: Whoa.
-JOEL: Oops.
RICK: Open the door!
-CROW: But not with your skull.
-SHARON: Molly!
-MOLLY: What's happened?
-SHARON: It's Kathy.
TOM: She's zestfully dead.
[ Tom chuckling ]
TOM: Ow.
MOLLY: Quickly, get her
onto the bed.
JOEL: Uh, you know,
this might sound crass,
but we're getting
really good at this.
CROW: They're going to have
to build an addition
just to stack the bodies.
SHARON: What's happening here?
TOM: How big
is a cord of bodies?
What was that thing?
CROW: Depends on how you
stack them.
BILL: Some kind of weird animal.
-Where are Brian and Tracy?
-JOEL: What have I done?
JOEL: What have I done?
Oh, my goodness.
TOMMY: Trumpy,
what are you doing here?
-Go on.
-TOM: Killing people.
-Tommy?
-JOEL: Can you hear me?
-Tommy!
-JOEL: Can you feel me near you?
TOMMY: We can't play now.
Something's happened downstairs.
You've gotta hide.
CROW: You're my alibi, kid.
TOM: They'll kill you.
They'll kill you dead.
[ Sniffs ]
JOEL: This thing smells musty.
-MOLLY: Tommy.
-What is it, Mom?
-Are you all right, son?
-Mm-hm.
CROW: Well, relatively speaking,
yes.
Depends on what the norm is.
RICK: Are you sure we ought
to go after it now, Bill?
Now's the time to finish
the damn thing off.
Once and for all.
It's wounded,
and we can follow its trail.
Don't go, Rick.
Isn't it better to wait
till morning?
I tell you, Molly. Now is
the time to finish it off.
But, Bill, why don't you leave
it for the rangers?
Isn't it their...?
Molly, we can't just sit here
waiting for it to come back
and kill us all.
TOM: Yeah, we got plenty
of booze. Let's go ahead.
BILL: And we gotta do it now.
It's not a monster.
It wants to be our friend.
How can you say that
after all that's happened?
'Cause it's true.
They all want to be our friends,
but we won't let them.
That's enough talking...
JOEL: Oh, that's silly.
Finish your tequila.
RICK: Don't worry.
We'll be careful.
Don't go. There's been
enough killing.
CROW: Stop the madness!
TOM: Last call, everybody.
Finish them up.
You coming or not?
TOM: Ah, we'll take a bottle.
Got a hip flask in the car.
JOEL: Hey, he's mixing
his leathers now.
TOM: Eww!
CROW: Wonder what they wanted?
Hmm?
[ Tom humming ]
MOLLY: Sharon! Tommy! Both
of you, quickly, come over here!
Get away from it!
[ Tom chuckling ]
Oh, my God!
TOMMY: No, Mommy.
Don't shoot him.
Tommy!
Trumpy is good.
It wasn't him.
JOEL: What he's done is good.
MOLLY: Tommy, get away from it!
No, Mommy, don't shoot.
Please.
TOM: Don't make your mother
kill him.
Tommy, it's going to kill you!
CROW: I know what you're
thinking, Tommy.
"Did mom fire six shots
or only five?"
MOLLY: Tommy!
[ Drums ]
JOEL: John Bonham. Moby Dick.
-MOLLY: Tommy! Tommy, come back!
-TOM: Shane! Come back, Shane!
Come back! Tommy!
-CROW: Run, Rusty, run.
-TOM: Run, Eliza, run.
JOEL: You know, that Trumpy
is one ugly...
CROW & TOM: Shut yo' mouth!
JOEL: Hey, I'm only talking
about Trumpy, can you dig it?
BILL: We have to cross over
to the other side.
Let's go.
TOM: Break on through
to the other side, man.
[ Tom laughs ]
CROW: Buddy Rich on drums.
TOM: Backed up
by Bill Kreutzmann.
MOLLY: Tommy! Tommy!
Where are you?
TOM: Fortunately, Molly
was a LLRP in 'Nam
and knows how to track
a boy with a snout-nosed pal.
BILL: I walked down stream
in the water.
It's a clever...
We'll never find him now.
Tommy!
We must go faster.
CROW: Yeah, yeah,
keep your shirt on.
I'm wearing a big stuffed suit.
RICK: Not a trace.
TOM: Who?
RICK: We'll have to wait
till daylight.
CROW: Daylight looks
like night anyhow.
What's it now?
TOM: Day for night, I think.
Oh. Thank you, Truffaut.
JOEL: Well, let's go home.
Our job is done here.
TOMMY: Someone's coming.
Get down.
CROW: Splendor in the grass.
TOM: Grazing in the grass
is a gas.
JOEL: Can you dig it?
CROW: High-weed surfin'.
TOMMY: Ssh.
TOM: Ssh. Would you...
Would you...
TOMMY: They mustn't find us.
[ Tom coughs ]
-TOM: Vapor action.
-Trumpy.
Trumpy, where are you hiding?
[ Whistling theme
from "Lassie" ]
[ Tom coughing ]
TOM: Boy, he's going to need
that gas mask.
CROW: Oh, Trumpy, gross.
TOM: You stepped
in some Trumpy-dumpy.
JOEL: You guys, come on.
[ Gasps ]
[ Continues to gasp ]
JOEL: Whoops.
[ Chuckles ] TOM: I'm gonna
batter fry you, kid.
CROW: Come on, over the plate,
man.
Mommy!
CROW: Come on, rocket it in,
man. Over the plate. Come on.
-Trumpy!
-TOM: Kid, you were set up.
TOMMY: Mommy!
RICK: Sounded like Tommy.
CROW: No, it wasn't.
It was "Mommy."
It was an "M" sound. "Mmm,"
like Manhattan, Mimosa.
MOLLY: Tommy!
Tommy, where are you?
JOEL: This is, like,
more intense
than when Bobby Brady got lost
in the Grand Canyon!
TOM: Oh, no, wasn't that
in Hawaii?
JOEL: No, that was where Peter
found that Buddha thing.
-CROW: Oh, yeah. That was cool.
-TOM: Oh, yeah.
TOMMY: Don't hurt me.
I'm not like the others.
[ Tom & Joel mewing ]
CROW: Ouch.
[ Tom continues mewing ]
TOMMY: I'll help you.
I'm not just one of them.
That's all.
Let me see.
CROW: Stay away from that.
It still hurts.
TOMMY: I'm sorry. Don't worry.
I'd just like to help you.
JOEL: I conspire against my own.
[ Tom mewing ]
RICK: No.
I'll blast one.
You take the other.
No, please don't hurt them.
Get out of the way, Tommy.
Get out of the way!
No, don't hurt them, please.
TOM: Move it, kid. I'll have
a banana daiquiri, please.
TOMMY: Run, Trumpy. Run!
No, Bill!
[ Screams ]
TOM: Long Island iced tea.
[ Creature screams ]
JOEL: Hey, looks like he came
from the Dumbo planet.
CROW: Time to take the mask off
and see who it is.
Do you folks at home know?
MOLLY: Tommy!
CROW: Oh, my ankle.
It's all bendy-wendy.
SHARON: Molly, we'll find him.
TOM: We may find him dead,
but we will find him.
JOEL: Boy, I hope he left
the keys to the liquor cabinet.
TOM: Poor sap.
CROW: Oh, self-bury monster.
Explain that.
TOM: Soft beach.
SHARON: Oh.
JOEL: And he died as he lived,
with his mouth wide open.
MOLLY: Where's Tommy?
He went that way.
Wait, Molly! Come on.
Trumpy, I'm sorry.
Tommy!
Tommy, answer me, please!
CROW: State it in the form
of a question.
-Tommy! Where are you?
-TOM: Come to the mirror, boy!
TOM: Mm-hm.
TOMMY: It's just no good.
No, Trumpy.
They'll never let us stay
together.
You frighten them.
You understand?
TOM: For obvious reasons.
I'll never forget you, Trumpy.
TOM: The way you callously
knocked off 15 people.
I'll never forget that.
Don't ever change, Trumpy.
Aww.
JOEL: A tender moment.
[ Weeping ]
TOMMY: Now, please go
and don't come back.
Do you understand?
Don't ever come back.
Tommy, where are you?
Go away, Trumpy.
I hate you. Go away.
JOEL: Oh, boy, that kid's
really having mood swings.
-We're not friends anymore.
-JOEL: That's not good.
TOMMY: Go away.
All right, Trumpy.
[ Tom mewing ]
I'll go, then.
I'm over here, Mommy.
CROW: Talkin' to Billy Barty.
[ Tom mewing ]
Mommy, I'm here!
TOM: Uh-huh.
RICK: Molly, he's here.
JOEL: No, he's over there.
MOLLY: Tommy!
Mom!
TOM: Sorry, boy,
your uncle's dead,
but if there's a God
and he tends bar,
your uncle's bellying up
right about now.
RICK: Yes, Tommy,
all the monsters are dead.
Isn't that right?
[ Synth music plays ]
TOM:
It's been seven
Oh, never mind.
CROW: Hey, don't leave me here.
I was raised by a child.
I can't survive
in the wilderness.
[ Tom mewing ]
I'll... just... wait here, then.
[ Mewing continues ]
TOM: So...
[ Sighs ]
CROW: Hmm.
TOM: Mm-hm.
JOEL:
I've laughed with monsters
JOEL & TOM:
I've cried with monsters
JOEL & TOM: I'll die
with monsters from hell
CROW: I'm getting out of here.
This place sucks.
[ Tom chuckles ]
CROW: Going back to my planet.
TOM: Hmm, Marine?
[ Chuckling ]
Send in the marines.
CROW: Hey.
JOEL: Ah, isn't that
Martin Sheen's son?
CROW: Hey, who isn't?
-JOEL: Yeah, got a point there.
-TOM: Yep.
TOM: Ooh, that's a good
Italian lunch wine.
Very light.
Smooth palate,
a nice woody finish.
JOEL: Hey, Martin and Lewis
were in this movie.
CROW: Come on, Jerry,
we've got the rest
of the credits to get through.
JOEL: Wow, Dean.
CROW: Aw, quit horsing around,
boy.
[ Tom sniffs ]
TOM: Ah, the fresh smell
of Emanuel Pine.
CROW: Long needle.
JOEL: I say both of those guys
were in the Knights of Columbus.
TOM: I think their Two Guys of
the Rotten Union is what it is.
CROW: Well, hmm.
TOM: Oh, I thought
I smelled basil.
Basil!
CROW: Yes, dear.
I'm doing it, dear.
How can I do it if you keep
calling me?
CROW: Great cow!
JOEL: Come on,
let's get out of here.
CROW: Oh, thank you.
TOM: Chase me.
CROW: Okay, ha ha ha.
Well, guys,
looks like it's time
to pack it all in again.
Yeah, we are the stuff
dreams are made of.
TOM: Oh, that's beautiful, Crow.
-Shakespeare?
-Uh, no, Burma-Shave.
Oh, well, Iike... Huh?
You know, guys, it always
hurts to close it all up...
-Yeah.
-...strike the set...
-Oww!
-...wipe off the grease paint...
Uh, napkin up
the blood and entrails
and move on to another town.
Uh-oh, I smell a song.
Mm-hm.
Tell me, where does
all the magic go
When the curtain falls
to end the show?
Do the clowns always cry
When they pack up
the paper sky?
When the champagne
is being poured
And the lock is on the old
stage door?
Will there still be a clown
in the sky
For me?
[ Sobbing ]
No.
Don't worry, buddy. There'll be
other experiments.
You really think so, mister?
Yeah, take a verse.
It'll cheer you up.
Okay.
When the harlequin
is on the bed
And the whisky haze
surrounds his head
William Holden's
coming over
-Tom Servo...
-And he's got a fifth of...
if you don't stop doing
your Anthony Newley,
I'm going to throw you
against the wall.
He'll do it, too.
Will there still be a clown
in the sky?
Help us out, Crow.
Still be a clown
in the sky?
Take it home, Joel.
Tell me, where is
that clown in the sky
For... me?
[ Sobbing ]
Oh!
I love you, Tom Servo.
-I love you, Joel.
-I love you, Crow.
You're not my real father.
What do you think, sirs?
It stinks.
Well?